[Music]
[Applause]
can't stop to
Chop Chop I'm could win choose not to
life of imitation this the reservation
def the P that you pay for this P the
feeling that you stay for any time I
want to be your best friend East Side
love is living on the west knocked out
you better come to don't die you know
the truth is to go write your message on
the payment look so right I wonder what
the r white he is dreaming in J go
complete the motion if you stumble go
ask the desper
ansers what I love the tears I to be
part of the wave can stop everyone do
this
[Music]
oh the world I love the CH I to be part
of Way St com me when it's time
to Sweet heart is bleeding in the snow
con so smart she leading me to O new the
great communicator you to to make it in
nature I'll get you into penetration the
genter of the generation the B of every
of the nation with your weight to go to
meditation this chap is going to be a
close one smoke wings and know you going
to blow one all on the SPAC you with the
be use my hat for anything but steering
they the spirit when they meet you my
tops are happy when they beat you J but
fers in the tree
[Music]
top I love the tears that drop to be
part of the wave St ever wonder with
it's all for you the world I love the
trains i h to be part of the wave stop
come and tell me when it's time to
wait a minute I'm passing out when all
lose just like
you almost shocking in anything I ever
knew how about
you tell my reason why I need somebody
new just like you
almost shocking in anything I ever
KN right
[Music]
[Applause]
don't stop addicted to the dick CH
says I'm going to win Cho not to the
limitation this C do
the the P that you pay for this pum the
feeling that you stay for in time I want
to be a best he I love his living on the
west knocked out you better come don't
die you know that you they got your on
the pement so I wonder what the wa kick
start to go the generator sweet talk but
don't Intimidator get stop the goost
from engineering use my hands for that
they my theory your image in the
dictionary this life is more than
ordinary can I get to maybe even three
of these coming from a space to teach
you with the be can't stop the spirits
when they need you this life is more
than just a read
[Applause]
[Music]
through going to get your hand to that
on just be
S my do you want to your light on take a
look it's on
display for you coming down on not
today did you me
your get it up with no propella do it up
it's way to fin smell picking up but not
too strong for you take a pie and pass
it all
fly away all my
Z I feel it
more and in this P WEA we find the place
together
[Music]
fly
re find a way to be a
deliver to the superly avator to
be for you take a look it's on
[Music]
display away all
my I feel it more than
ever and in this
P we find a place together
the water s my
emotion on the road to pass me
by away all
my we found a place together
[Music]
w w w
w to you yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah wo w w w w
wo you yeah yeah yeah
yeah fly all
my I feeling more than
ever
that with
the
[Music]
together
emotion all the world pass me by F away
all
my when live
[Music]
[Applause]
w
[Music]
I'm a dance hall in your bedroom make
you feel W make you want to
resume now we
know it
all for
sure I'm a notion let it break me make
the Stow fall up from underneath be not
[Music]
alone now be there tell me when you want
to
[Music]
go I'm a me l First reab Take It All of
and step inside the running C there's a
love
know the
way I'm the rainbow in your CH cell all
the memory of everything youve ever
smell not
alone I'll be there tell me when you
want to
[Music]
[Applause]
don't me
I come again get me
[Music]
[Applause]
ex I'm an in bread and a p head two legs
that you spread inside the T shed now we
know it all for
sure I can show you to the
free overcome and more be
re not
alone I'll be there tell me when you
want to go
[Music]
oh don't forget me
I come again I get me
[Applause]
[Music]
excited sh my
on the blood stain on your shirts s
coming down and more coming to
believe now we
know it
all for
sure I'll make the hair stand up on your
WR did you how to dance inside the
phon not
alone I'll be there tell me when you
want to go
I'll be there tell me when you want to
go
[Music]
we